{
    "subject": "Param_Gill",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Hotel_Hollywood",
    "human_readable": "Param Gill created Hotel Hollywood.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8282248377799988,
            "question": "What is the name of the hotel Param Gill created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7943853139877319,
            "question": "Who created Hotel Hollywood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6958571672439575,
            "question": "What type of establishment did Param Gill create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6153717041015625,
            "question": "When was Hotel Hollywood created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5687916874885559,
            "question": "What else has Param Gill created or been involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.334331750869751,
            "question": "Where is Hotel Hollywood located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33408665657043457,
            "question": "What services does Hotel Hollywood offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31450819969177246,
            "question": "Is there any other information available about Hotel Hollywood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2756902575492859,
            "question": "Is there a website for Hotel Hollywood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26220008730888367,
            "question": "Who can I contact for more information about Hotel Hollywood?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Param Gill created Hotel Hollywood.",
            "html": "yago_19133_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a website for Hotel Hollywood?",
            "html": "yago_19133_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any other information available about Hotel Hollywood?",
            "html": "yago_19133_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What services does Hotel Hollywood offer?",
            "html": "yago_19133_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19133_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19133_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19133_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19133_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19133_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19133_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19133_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19133_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19133_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_19133_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The documents mention \"Hotel Hollywood\" as a movie directed by Param Gill and Sandeep Singh (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_19133/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt).\n* The same documents also mention Param Gill releasing \"Hotel Hollywood\" in 2010 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_19133/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_19133/re-ranker-msmarco/85.txt).\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Param Gill being the director of \"Hotel Hollywood,\" which supports the statement that Param Gill created Hotel Hollywood."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}